Contact

johnguarra2@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/john-cloedguarra-92358417a (LinkedIn) www.upwork.com/freelancers/ ~01f12da62ffedf0e5d (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Google Ads

Social Media

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

Certifications

Google Ads - Measurement Certification

HubSpot Marketing Software

Google Ads Search Certification

Google Analytics Individual Qualification

John Cloed Guarra

Web Developer, Social Media Manager, and Ads Expert.

Summary

Technical skills

- HTML
- · CSS, CSS3
- jQuery
- PHP
- MySQL
- Proficient in Microsoft Office products

Certified Google Ads and Facebook Ads specialist who has 3+ years of experience and managed different campaigns for different types of businesses. Help in achieving clients' digital and social media marketing goals, allowing to have a better understanding of how their business performs and generate outstanding results and progress.

Expertise includes:

- Digital marketing
- Google ads/PPC
- Facebook and Instagram Ads
- Social media Manager
- Certified HubSpot Marketing Software Expert
- Certified Canva Designer
- Google Analytics
- Website design and development
- Content Creation
- Video Editing

Experience

Fiverr

Graphic Designer

February 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Tel Aviv, Israel

Upwork

3 years 1 month

Website Developer, Digital Marketer and Data Entry Assistant August 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months)

San Francisco, California, United States

Digital Marketing Specialist June 2019 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Education

Camarines Norte State College
Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (2020 - 2022)

Microsystem College Foundation Inc.

Grade 12, Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2018 - 2020)